Guide to the Dept. of Music Records, 1922-Ongoing UA.25.28.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Dept. of Music records
1922-Ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Department of Music
UA.25.28.0002
17.6 Linear Feet
The Department of Aesthetics, Art & Music was established at Duke University in 1942. In 1960, the Department of Music was recognized as an independent department and Dr. Allen H. Bone was appointed the first Chair. The department moved into the Mary Duke Biddle Music Building when it was completed in the 1970's. The bulk of the Dept. of Music records consist of publicity documents including programs, press releases, and calendars, for various Dept. of Music events. There are also documents regarding the renovation of the facilities, clippings, posters and general records for the department.
Access Restrictions
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Electronic records in this collection have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact a reference archivist before coming to use these records.
Provenance
The Dept. of Music Records were received by the University Archives as a transfer starting in 1975.
Historical Note
The Department of Aesthetics, Art & Music was established at Duke University in 1942. In 1960, the Department of Music was recognized as an independent department and Dr. Allen H. Bone was appointed the first Chair. The Mary Duke Biddle Music Building, completed in the 1970s, became the Department of Music's permanent home.
Today, the Department of Music thrives as a presence that is felt throughout campus. With nine performing ensembles (Chamber Music, Chorale, Collegium Musicum, Djembe, New Music, Jazz, Opera Workshop, Symphony Orchestra and Wind Symphony) and hundreds of students enrolled in classes, the Department of Music pursues its mission to enrich the educational experience of all Duke students.
Collection Overview
The bulk of the Dept. of Music records consist of publicity documents including programs, press releases, and calendars, for various Dept. of Music events. There are also documents regarding the renovation of the facilities, clippings, posters and general records for the department.
Related Material
Allan H. Bone Papers, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Duke University. Dept. of Aesthetics, Art, and Music; Duke University. Dept. of Music
- Container List 1922-Ongoing
  Scope and Contents note
  Much of the content in this collection has been published or distributed, however any administrative records that have not been published are restricted for 25 years from their point of origin. Please contact research services for more information.
  - Durham Civic Choral Society, 1948-1964 (Box 1)
  - Durham Civic Choral Society, 1982-1958 (Box 1)
  - Durham Civic Choral Society, 1961-1964 (Box 1)
  - Transylvania Music Camp Programs, 1950-1955 (Box 1)
  - Raleigh Chamber Music Guild, before 1960 (Box 1)
  - Music for Organ and Orchestra, before 1960 (Box 1)
  - An Evening of Music for the Theater by Monteverdi, 1968 February 25 (Box 1)
  - A Sonata Recital: Di Cecco & Friedberg, 1968 March 12 (Box 1)
  - Souvenir Programs: National Music Camp (Interlochen), undated (Box 1)
  - Souvenir Programs: University of Wisconsin, 1931-1949 (Box 1)
  - Dedication of Biddle Music Building, October, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Collegium Musicum: Clippings & Programs, 1974-1978 (Box 1)
  - Music Department: Clippings, 1980-1989 (Box 1)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra Concert, 1954; 1963-1968 (Box 2)
  - Duke Concert Band, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Duke Madrigal Singers, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra Concert, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Music With Organ, Symphony or Little Symphony, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Duke Concert Band, 1962-1964 (Box 2)
  - Duke Madrigal Singers, With Marjorie Randolph and the Duke Recorders, 1963 October 29 (Box 2)
  - Duke Concert Band, 1964-1968 (Box 2)
  - Duke Madrigal Singers, 1963-1972 (Box 2)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, With Susan Starr, 1963 December 17 (Box 2)
  - Small Orchestra Concert, 16-Feb-68 (Box 2)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra (Season Tickets and Calendars), 1963-1978 (Box 2)
  - Jazz Ensemble, circa 1976 (Box 2)
  - Music Department Minutes & Faculty Events, 1972-1977 (Box 2)
  - Newsletters: "Music at Duke", 1978-1979 (Box 2)
  - Requested Move of Music Collections from East Campus Library, 1968-1974 (Box 3)
  - Biddle Music Building: Installation of Fixtures and Musical Instruments, 1973-1975 (Box 3)
  - Chronicle Article on Closing of Asbury, 7-Dec-73 (Box 3)
  - Closing of Asbury and Relocation of Music Department, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Renovation of East Duke Building, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Biddle Music Building: Ground-breaking, 1972 February 28 (Box 3)
  - Room Notes, circa 1975 (Box 3)
  - Programs - Master File, 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Programs - Master File, 1974-1975 (Box 4)
  - Programs - Master File, 1975-1976 (Box 4)
  - Programs - Master File, 1977-1982 (Box 4)
  - Graduate Studies Leaflet, circa 1981 (Box 4)
  - Circulars, Announcements, Leaflets, 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  - Calendars, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1976-1978 (Box 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1978-1979 (Box 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 5)
  - Programs - Master File, 1967-1970 (Box 5)
  - Programs - Master FIle, 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra: Records and Programs, 1946-1963 (Box 6)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra: Records and Programs, 1964-1975 (Box 6)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra: Records and Programs, 1976-1983 (Box 6)
  - Music Department Records, 1981-1982 (Box 6)
  - Music Department Records, 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Music Department Records, 1983-1984 (Box 6)
  - Music Department Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 6)
  - Programs, Sponsored by Department, 1963-1984 (Box 7)
  - Department of Aesthetics, Art, Music (Miscellaneous Information), 1947-1957 (Box 7)
  - Department of Aesthetics, Art, Music (Programs), 1956-1958 (Box 7)
  - Duke University Chamber Orchestra and Chamber Music Programs, before 1960 (Box 7)
  - Duke University Alumni Register, 1954 (Box 7)
  - Raleigh Chamber Music Guild, 1961-1962 (Box 7)
  - Mary Duke Biddle Lectures, 1961-1964 (Box 7)
  - Ernst Krenek Festival - N.C. Music Society, 1963-1964 (Box 7)
  - John Duke Lecture-Recital, 1963 November 5 (Box 7)
  - Student Union Young Artist Series - Susan Starr, Pianist, 1963 November 20 (Box 7)
  - Fourth Annual Duke Music Conference - Lukas Foss, 1965 February 11 (Box 7)
  - Fourth Annual Duke Music Conference - Program, 1965 February (Box 7)
  - Fourth Annual Duke Music Conference - Milton Babbitt, 1965 February 19 (Box 7)
  - Fifth Annual Music Conference, 1966 February (Box 7)
  - Music Conference - Duke Festival of the Contemporary Arts, 1967 February (Box 7)
  - Seventh Annual Music Conference - Composers' Conference, 1968 February (Box 7)
  - Eighth Annual Music Conference, 1969 February (Box 7)
  - Tenth Annual Music Conference, 1971 February (Box 7)
  - Twelfth Annual Music Conference, 1973 February (Box 7)
  - Music Educators Conferences, 1963-1964 (Box 7)
  - Music Teachers National Association, 1964 April (Box 7)
  - Department of Aesthetics Programs, 1949-1950 (Box 8)
  - Calendar of Musical Events, 1966, undated (Box 8)
  - Calendar of Musical Events, before 1966 (Box 8)
  - Faculty Recitals, before 1960 (Box 8)
  - Faculty Recitals, 1961-1963 (Box 8)
  - Faculty Recitals, 1964-1965 (Box 8)
  - Faculty Recitals, 1966-1968 (Box 8)
  - Faculty Recitals, 1968-1970s (Box 8)
  - Sonata Recital: Ciompi & Loesser, 1968 May 4 (Box 8)
  - Ciompi-Withers Duo Programs, 1964-1968 (Box 8)
  - Ciompi Quartet and North Carolina String Quartet, 1967-1970 (Box 8)
  - Allan H. Bone: Guest Conductor or Performing (Souvenir Programs), 1947-1960 (Box 8)
  - Iain Hamilton Recitals, 1962-1968 (Box 8)
  - Frances Redding Recital, 1967 October 29 (Box 8)
  - Souvenir Programs, 1952-1977 (Box 9)
  - Opera Presentations, 1964-1979 (Box 9)
  - Clippings & Programs (miscellaneous), 1936-1976 (Box 9)
  - Recital Programs, 1958-1959 (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Recital Programs, 1959-1960 (3 folders) (Box 10)
  - Recital Programs, 1961-1962 (3 folders) (Box 10)
  - Student Recitals, before 1962 (Box 10)
  - Student Recital (Students of John Hanks), 1963 (Box 10)
  - Student Recitals, 1964-1965 (Box 10)
  - Student Recitals, 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Student Recitals, 1968-1977 (Box 10)
  - Senior Piano Recital: Billie Godwin, Diana Bess Montgomery, 1963-1964 (Box 10)
  - Student Recital: Leslie Withers, Flute, 1967 April 22 (Box 10)
  - Student Recital: Frances Dick, Piano, 1967 May 16 (Box 10)
  - Student Recital: John Ruggero, Piano, 1967 May 21 (Box 10)
  - Student Recital: Kaye Franklin, Violin, 1967 February 15 (Box 10)
  - Student Recital: Kern Holoman, Bassoon, 1968 March 17 (Box 10)
  - Student Recital: Jerry Jernigan & Betty Milspaw, 1968 May 10 (Box 10)
  - Student Recital: Students of Loren Withers, 1961-1966 (Box 10)
  - Voice Recitals by Students of John Hanks, 1965-1967 (Box 10)
  - Recitals by Students of Paul Earls, 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Student Recital, Sponsored by Delta Mu Tau, 1965-1967 (Box 10)
  - Flyers, Programs and Announcements, 1984-1986 (Box 11)
  - Flyers, Programs and Announcements, 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Press Clippings: Arts & Music, 1987-1991 (Box 11)
  - Duke Notes - Newsletter, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 1987-1998 (Box 11)
  - Opera Festivals, 1977-1982 (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous Music & Arts, 1982-1992 (Box 11)
  - Programs, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
  - Calendars & Brochures, 1996-1997 (Box 11)
  - Programs, 2000-2001 (Box 11)
  - Printed Matter, 1996-1997 (3 folders) (Box 12)
  - Printed Matter - Events, 1997-1998 (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Printed Matter, 1998-1999 (3 folders) (Box 13)
  - Printed Matter, 1999-2000 (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Jazz Ensemble, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Graduation, Silbiger Retirement, Hip Hop Conference, J.K. Hanks Service, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Collegium Musicum, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Djembe / Afro-Cuban Drumming, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Organ Recitals, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Encounters, Milestones Concerts, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Lecture Series, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Guest Recitals & Masterclasses, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Calendars, Audition Information, String School, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Graduate Composers Concerts, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Parents Weekend Concerts, 2001-2002 (Box 14)
  - Duke Chorale, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Duke Chapel Lunchtime Concerts, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Eddy Collection, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Faculty Recitals, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Opera Workshop, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Student Recitals, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Auditions, Fall 2003 (Box 15)
  - Calendars, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Duke Chorale, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Collegium Musicum, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Djembe Ensemble, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Encounters Series, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Jazz Ensemble, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Masterclasses, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Lecture Series, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Chapel Lunchtime Concerts, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Guest & Faculty Recitals, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Student Recitals, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Parents Weekend Concerts, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Opera Workshop, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Music Conferences - SEHKS, AMIS, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Music Department - Graduation, 2004 (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Audition Information and Season Calendars, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Collegium Musicum, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Concert for Brodhead Inauguration, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Detten-Bijl Collection of Musical Instruments, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Djembé Ensemble, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Duke Chorale, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Faculty Recitals, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Festival of Piano - Four Hands, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - French Opera Symposium, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Graduate Composers Concerts, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Graduation, 2005 (Box 16)
  - Guest Recitals, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Jazz Ensemble, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Lecture Series, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Master Classes, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Mendelssohn: A Life in Music by R. Larry Todd, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Milestones: A Festival of New Music, 2004 (Box 16)
  - Opera Workshop, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Organ Recitals, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Parents Weekend Concerts, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Prism Concert, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Student Recitals, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - South Central Graduate Music Consortium, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Wind Symphony, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - Media Coverage, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Concerts, 1988-1989 (Box 17)
  - Programs, 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - Media, 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - Office of Performing Organizations, 1990-1991 (Box 17)
  - Programs, 1990-1991 (Box 17)
  - Office of Performing Organizations, printed matter, 1991-1996 (multiple folders) (Box 17)
  - Programming, 1976-1987 (13 folders) (Box 18)
  - Graduation, 2006 (Box 19)
  - Prism Concert, April 2006 (Box 19)
  - Festival of Four Hands Piano, 2006 (Box 19)
  - Graduate Composers, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Opera Workshop, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Byrd Conference, Fall 2005 (Box 19)
  - Collegium Musicum, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Djembe Ensemble, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Guest Recitals, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Parents Weekend, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Encounters Series, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - String School, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Ciompi Quarter, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - DUMIC, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - "World on Music" Conference, 2005 (Box 19)
  - Music Department, Faculty Recitals, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Duke Chorale, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Student Recitals, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Master Classes, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Lecture Series, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Jazz Ensemble, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Calendars, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Auditions, 2005-2006 (Box 19)
  - Duke Chorale, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Masterclasses, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Calendars, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Auditions, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Very Old Programs, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 20)
  - Alumni Weekend Prism Concert, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Jazz Ensemble, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Jazz Ensemble, Louie Bellson, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Graduate Composer, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Chamber Music Ensemble, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Opera Workshop, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Collegium Musicum, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Djembe Ensemble, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Parents and Family Weekend, 2006 (Box 20)
  - Organ Recitals, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Duke University String School, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Music Faculty Performances, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Ciompi Quartet, Duke Performances, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Lecture Series, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Rare Music Series (DUMIC), 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Student Recitals, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Encounters Series, Milestones Festival and New Music, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Guest Artist Recitals, 2006-2007 (Box 20)
  - Duke University String School, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Duke Chorale, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Lecture Series, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Student Recitals, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Piano Students and Faculty, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Master Classes, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Graduation, 2008 (Box 21)
  - PRISM Concert, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Graduate Composers (Box 21)
  - Opera Workshop and Voice Area Information, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Student Chamber Music, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Symphony Orchestra, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Collegium Musicum, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Faculty Recitals, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Wind Symphony, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Duke University Musical Instrument Collections (DUMIC), 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Duke New Music Ensemble (DNME), 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Encounters: With the Music of Our Time, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Jazz Ensemble, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Djembe Ensemble, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Parents Weekend Concerts, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Washington National Opera, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Calendars, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - Music Dept. Auditions, 2007-2008 (Box 21)
  - G. Norman and Ruth G. Eddy Collection of Musical Instruments Promotional Materials, 2002-2004, undated (Box 22)
  - Alumni Information, 1994-2009, undated (Box 22)
  - Duke Notes Publication, 1995-2004, undated (Box 22)
  - Concert Programs, Posters and Advertisements, 1967-1998 (3 folders) (Box 22)
  - Publications and Brochures, 1922-2006 (Box 22)
  - Faculty Press Clippings and Publicity, 1987-1993 (Box 22)
  - Programs, 2000-2001 (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - National Opera Company, 1978-1980 (Box 22)
  - Information about Alumni, 11994, undated (Box 22)
  - Collegium Musicum, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Graduation, 2010 (Box 22)
  - Duke Chorale, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Opera Workshop, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Djembe Ensemble, 2009 (Box 22)
  - Graduate Composers Concerts, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Student Chamber Music, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Parents' Weekend Concerts, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Encounters: With the Music of our Time, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Guest Recitals and Concerts, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Duke New Music Ensemble, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Faculty Recitals, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Student Recitals, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Master Classes, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Lecture Series, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Jazz Ensemble, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - DUMIC Rare Music Series, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Calendars and Audition Schedules, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Brochures, circa 1980s-1990s (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - C.D. of Digital Versions of Promotional Materials, 2009-2010 (Box 22)
  - Videocassette: Duke Online Sampler 2, 1992-1993, 1. Henry Petroski, 2. African American Dance Ensemble, 3. Dr. Dorie Reents (Box 22)
  - Oversize Posters for Various Music Department Events, 2009-2010 (Box 23)
  - Oversize Posters for Various Music Department Events, 2008-2009 (Box 23)
  - Duke New Music Ensemble, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Russian Music Project, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Faculty Recitals, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Wind Symphony, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Parent and Family Weekend, 2008 (Box 24)
  - Guest Artist Recitals, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Duke University, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Duke University Musical Instrument Collections and Rare Music Series, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Jazz, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Auditions and Classes, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Lecture Series, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Master Classes, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Brochures, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Student Recitals, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Duke Chorale, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Graduation, 2009 (Box 24)
  - Opera Workshop, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Collegium Musicum, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Djembe Ensemble, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Student Chamber Music, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Graduate Composers, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - "Encounters" With New Music Series, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Compact Disc of Programs, Brochures, Photos and Other, 2008-2009 (Box 24)
  - Auditions, Announcements, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Collegium Musicum, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Department Promotional Items, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Djembe Ensemble, 2010 (Box 25)
  - Duke Jazz Ensemble, Frank Foster Concert, 2010 (Box 25)
  - Duke Musical Instruments Collection Events, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Duke New Music Ensemble, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Duke Chorale, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Duke-UNC Chopin/Schumann Festival, 2010 (Box 25)
  - Encounters witth the Music of our Time, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Events Calendar, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Faculty Recitals, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Graduate Composers Concerts, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Guest Recitals, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Master Classes, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Monteverdi Vespers, 2010 (Box 25)
  - Graduation, 2011 (Box 25)
  - Opera Workshop, 2011 (Box 25)
  - {arents and Family Weekend, 2010 (Box 25)
  - South Central Graduate Musci Consortium Conference, 2010 (Box 25)
  - String School, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Student Chamber Music, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Student Recitals, 2010-2011 (Box 25)
  - Tonality Conference, 2010 (Box 25)
  - Family Weekend Concert, 2011 (Box 26)
  - Advertising and Auditions, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Calendars and Brochures, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Collegium Musicum, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Djembe Ensemble, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Duke Chorale, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Duke New Music Ensemble, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Duke University String School, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Encounters Series, Wet Ink Ensemble, Graduate Composers, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Faculty Recitals, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Guest Recitals, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Lecture Series in Musicology, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Master Classes, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Opera Workshop, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Organ Recitals, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Student Chamber Music, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Student Recitals, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Ciompi Quartet, Summer Series, 2012 (Box 26)
  - Graduation, 2012 (Box 26)
  - Ragtime, 2012 (Box 26)
  - Compact discs of digital surrogates of publicity materials, 2010-2011, 2011-2012 (Box 26)
  - Event Posters, 2011-2012 (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Family Weekend, 2012 (Box 27)
  - Auditions, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Brochures and Calendars, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Chamber Music, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Chronicle Ads for Courses and Events, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Collegium Musicum, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Djembe and Afro-Cuban Ensembles, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Duke Chorale, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Duke University String School, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Encounters: With the Music of our Time, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Faculty and Guest Recitals, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Graduate Courses and Duke New Music Ensemble, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Jazz Ensemble, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Lectures and Conferences, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Master Classes, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Opera Workshop, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Student Recitals, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Symphony Orchestra, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Wind Symphony, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Graduation, 2013 (Box 27)
  - CD of digital surrogates, 2012-2013 (Box 27)
  - Event Posters, 2012-2013 (Oversize-folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1975-1979 (Box S.1)
  - Items Separated from scrapbook, Clippings, 1975-1979 (Box S.1)
  - Items Separated from Scrapbook, Programs, 1975-1979 (Box S.1)
  - Scrapbook, Jazz at Duke, 1924-1977 (Box S.1)
  - Items Separated from Scrapbook, 1979, undated (Box S.1)
  - Items Separated, Les Brown - Clippings, Photographs, 1969-1977 (Box S.1)
  - Jazz Combinations, 1974-1977 (Box S.1)
  - Jazz at Duke Scrapbook Loose Items and History of Duke Jazz Ensemble, 1924-1974 and undated (Box S.1)
  - Scrapbook, 1963-1967 (Box S.2)
  - Scrapbook, 1953-1957 (Box S.4)
  - Oversize Posters for Various Music Department Events, circa 2008-2009 (2 folders) (Box S.4)
  - Spring Arts Preview, 2014 (Box 28)
  - Music Advertising, Auditions, 2013-2014 (Box 28)